Downloaded from YTS.MX
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Do you think we're close?
They're almost
impossible to find.
No one's ever
captured one alive.
I agreed
to provide security for you...
because I thought you were close
to finding the spider.
Well, it's worth the wait.
Dead specimens show that
the peptides
in the spider's venom, they...
Basically, they supercharge
their cellular structure.
That spider can give
superhuman strength and power...
like 'Las Arañas'.
'Las Arañas'?
The mythical spider people
who run across the treetops...
and punish evil men
with their black,
poisoned touch?
I like to base my research
in science,
not legends, Mr Sims.
Those powers are wasted here.
These little spiders
have the potential
to cure hundreds of diseases.
It could...
- Are you okay?
- No.
She's trying her best
to keep me from working.
But I'm not
gonna let her do that.
Not when I'm this close.
Perhaps you should rest.
I don't have time.
Thank you.
For the umbrella.
I found it.
I found the spider.
- Isn't she beautiful?
- Wow.
- Incredible, isn't it?
- Constance.
Something so small
yet have so much power.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I don't...
I don't understand.
I've been searching
for that spider for years.
No, don't...
We could help so many people.
I'm not interested
in helping people.
No one helped me
when my family was starving.
My road was
not as clear as yours.
We didn't have the same choices.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- Give me the spider!
- No.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- Give it to me.
- No.
- No. Ezekiel.
- No. Please.
- You could just walk away.
No.
Her journey will not be easy...
but she is strong.
She will come back
when she needs answers.
And when she does...
I will be here for her.
Come on!
Move!
All right! All right!
This is 2-10
with a 42-year-old female.
Code three.
Cassie, I lost the pulse.
I'm starting compressions now.
Ben, what are you
even doing back there?
Oh, you wanna come take over?
I can drive.
She's not going
room temp on my watch.
Come on.
How you doing back there?
You know, last time I was
in a vehicle driven like this,
I was being shot at.
I wouldn't want you
to be homesick for the Army.
Never thought I'd be this happy
to be back in Queens.
What, you've never been
shot at in Queens?
Shouldn't you be in school?
Who flips off an ambulance?
Oh, you're gonna be okay.
Jesus.
Kids.
- I'm gonna get roped in.
- No, you're not.
You're gonna be in the backyard
grilling with us.
I know how
these things work, Ben.
Oh, do you? How do you know?
I bet you've never even
been to a baby shower.
Because, yeah,
I'm careful not to get roped in.
I'm glad I caught you
before you headed back out.
She's gonna be okay.
Who?
Your patient.
Her little boy
wanted to say thank you.
You know what,
Mr Ben Parker here
did all the work, so...
Just take it.
Take it.
- That's... I mean...
- Thank you.
- Thanks, buddy.
I'll take you in to see her.
- Are you all immediate family?
- Oh, my God.
I'm her stepdaughter.
I think she might prefer...
Yeah, it's okay, Dad.
I'll see you guys
back at your apartment?
Okay.
Come on, buddy.
Let's go see Mommy.
Okay. This one is for you.
This is for me.
- Thanks so much.
- You're welcome.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
Just put it in your pocket
and then throw it away
somewhere else.
Can't even fold it.
It's like cardboard.
Come on.
We both hate family stuff.
I think I have plans
anyways, so...
Plans? Since when
do you have plans?
You're, like,
impossible to pin down.
Well, I like
to keep my options open.
You know, I might sleep in.
I might go to the museum.
I might walk the dog.
You don't have a dog.
I might adopt one.
Return the favour.
I suspect you were a bit more
of a handful than a puppy.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I was a model foster kid.
I peed outside and everything.
So...
I kinda met someone.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
What's this one's name?
Serious.
She's a lucky lady, Ben.
Thank you.
"You have
a winning personality."
I guess I got yours by mistake.
You're an asshole.
Here.
Let's see what
your future holds for you.
What if I don't wanna know?
Well, it's just a cookie.
"You will."
You will what?
- Apparently, I have no future.
- Cassie.
- Do you know what this means?
- What?
It means that
their printer is broken.
We can't eat here any more.
Yeah, I'll meet you at
the coffee shop at the corner.
You think
I can manage both of these?
I think so, yeah.
We'll have it for you tomorrow.
My dad just needs
to pick up his paycheque.
Well, let me come in
and talk to your dad.
I haven't seen him in a while.
Maybe we can work something out.
He's not
home right now, actually.
Look, I'll be back tomorrow.
But no more excuses.
I swear. We'll have it.
All right.
Us strays
need to stick together.
Somebody's hungry.
Hope the spiders
were worth it, Mom.
For your own safety,
please stay where you are.
You gotta get, like,
Jaws of Life for that.
MVA, three vehicles.
One vehicle
flipped over with entrapment.
Copy that. Sending backup
to your location.
It won't open.
All right, sir. We're gonna
get you out of there, okay?
Just don't move.
Hi, sir.
Can you tell me your name?
Robert.
Robert, I'm Cassie.
I'm gonna help you out
today, okay?
You're gonna be all right.
All right,
I'm gonna cut your seat belt.
And when I do,
you're gonna fall...
and my partner Ben
is gonna help you out
on that side, okay?
Three, two, one.
All right, Robert.
We're gonna move on three.
- Okay? Here we go.
- Yeah.
One, two, three.
Okay. You're gonna be okay, sir.
Just try and lay still.
We're gonna get you checked...
- Hey! Cassie!
- Ben!
- Cassie!
79 over 55.
Dial it back, I'm fine.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital.
No, you were right.
They're roping ya in.
Games!
You guys are ice-cold.
Cassie!
This place has always
been a death trap.
You can't save all three!
...you can use the web
to be in more than one place
at the same time.
You are the only one
who can change the future.
No!
Cassie!
That's it, Cassie, breathe!
Come on!
You're okay. You're okay.
Did I die?
Yeah.
You were down three minutes
before I fished you out.
- Three minutes?
- Yeah.
Welcome back
to the land of the living.
You're not goin' anywhere.
79 over 55.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital
with a real doctor.
I don't need a doctor.
I trust you.
Ah, 80%. No, it's great.
Slightly above that
of a dead fish.
All right.
Well, O2 is going up to 89.
Jump back in the water anytime.
You're not goin' anywhere.
79 over 55.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital
with a real doctor.
Seriously, Ben, dial it back.
I'm fine.
Wait, wait, wait. I need
to get your oxygen levels.
Again?
What are you talking about?
My O2 is 89.
- Okay, stay back, stay back.
- No, it's...
Oh, you're right.
Are you okay?
What the hell
happened down there?
I'm fine.
I just wanna go home
and watch 'Idol'.
Please stay where you are.
Wow.
Great apartment.
Where's my spider?
They took my spider.
Who are you?
No!
Bad dream?
It's not a dream.
I'm gonna be murdered one day.
Oh, wow, that's a buzzkill.
The same three faces.
Every night, the same vision.
It's a curse.
But we all die someday.
Nothing we can really do
to stop that.
But if you saw
who was going to murder you...
you'd try to stop them.
Okay...
You have no idea
of the torment and torture...
of dying over and over again.
And I can't escape it.
So I'm not gonna sit back
and let it happen.
I will find them
and kill them first.
So you know who did it...
I mean, will do it?
It's always those three faces.
Can you imagine
how frustrating it's been?
Trying to identify someone
I've only seen in a vision?
But as the years pass...
there have been
technological advances.
New ways to find people,
if you know their faces.
The kind of technology
I've heard...
the National Security Agency
has been pursuing.
What are you doing?
How are you poisoning me?
What's your password?
I can't tell you. Oh, please!
Is "please" your password?
Tell me quickly before
the paralysis reaches your lips
and I'll stop the poison.
Q-9-2-0...
B-3-7-5.
Oh, God.
Believe me, it's a good thing
you had no idea...
today was the day
you were going to die.
- Hey, Cassie.
- Hey.
I'm serious. You should
open, like, a barbecue.
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
You know what you're doing.
- I saw him leave.
- Yeah, I...
Cassie!
- Hey!
- Hi.
Hey, the next time
you wanna go swimmin',
maybe you should
stick to Astoria Park.
Oh, that's really funny.
You're such a funny guy.
Are you pressing the burgers?
I'm releasin' the fat.
That's called flavour, man.
Plus, it's, like,
really flammable.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
You don't think that maybe
in light of recent events
I could use a beer?
Well, as you know,
the protocol is...
no booze within
24 hours of your death. So...
- Is that protocol?
- Yeah, it's protocol.
That's boring.
I feel like
there's more of a story there.
No, there's...
You guys,
we've seen this a hundred times.
It was cardiac arrest.
When your heart starts
back up again, you're fine.
Really?
Dead, huh?
Did you see a white light or...
Well, actually, I saw Jersey...
- so you tell me.
- Oh, come on, you saw...
- Hey.
She hit me with a Jersey joke.
Has he been
pressin' the burgers again?
Yeah, they're ruined now.
Take that. For you, sir.
- Oh, now they're really ruined.
- Oh, okay.
- We're ready to start.
- What?
What?
They're starting,
so you should get in there.
No, you were right,
they're roping ya in.
- Yeah. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Have fun.
- ...for you, okay.
- Hi. Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- Look at you. Hi.
Okay. This is crazy.
Well, I couldn't decide,
so I got two.
Yeah, that's like...
- Hey. Hi.
- Hi.
Cassie Webb.
Thanks for having me.
You're Ben's partner.
I'm his sister-in-law, Mary.
Nice to meet you.
Ben is so excited
about being an uncle.
I don't know
what we'd do without him.
- Especially with Richard away.
- Again.
Where is it this time?
He's in Mumbai...
Shanghai... I can't keep track.
Never stops
leaping around in there.
And always hungry.
Does it have a name? The...
We're saving that
for one of the games.
- Games?
- Games!
Games!
Okay.
"My mother always cut the crusts
off my sandwiches."
Chloe, is that you?
Yes.
My mom said the crusts
would make my hair go curly.
It was years
before I figured that one out.
Hold up. Hold up. Bernie!
Whose is this?
Oh, it's mine.
You must have at least
one fond memory of your mother.
Well, my mother
actually died in childbirth.
Well, but it wasn't that bad.
It wasn't like...
I mean, obviously,
it was bad, you know.
She died.
But, I grew up totally healthy.
Death in childbirth
is super rare.
I mean, she chose to be, like,
way deep in the Amazon...
for the last month
of her pregnancy...
hundreds of miles away from
any medical facilities, so...
Okay, so let's...
let's move on to the next game.
Guess the name of Mary's baby.
Oh, yes!
Okay, I'll kick things off.
- Sam.
- Nope.
Steven.
- He's not named Steven.
- Shoot.
- Baby sausage?
- You guys are ice-cold.
Baby sausage?
Richard Junior?
Richard wishes.
Get your hamburger.
Cassie... what's your guess?
Do that thing
where you throw it up
and catch it on the...
- Oh, my God.
- Ben?
- Look at that.
- The name is...
Baby sausage?
Richard Junior?
Richard wishes.
Come on, get your hamburger.
Get your...
Cassie... what's your guess?
Put five dollars down, let's go.
Wait. We just did this.
Do that thing
where you throw it up
and catch it on the...
What, seriously,
is this part of the game?
Sorry.
They're calling everyone in.
Fire down at the docks.
So...
You okay?
Yeah. I just got
a weird sense of déjà vu.
I got you, man.
I don't...
I don't think it's broken.
The ones who got out, come on.
This way.
Get her out. Come on.
Grabbin' a woman on A-side here.
Go. Go. Go.
We need more pressure
in the line.
Keep pressure on the leg
here, okay?
Okay, looks like
a fractured left radius.
Otherwise stable.
Wait, wait, wait.
Check his abdomen.
Okay, and internal injuries.
Good catch.
Let's go. Come on.
Hey, I need
to get my guys in there.
No, it's not safe.
The structure's unstable.
Hey, the people are trapped.
We need to treat 'em
before we move them.
The place is
packed with explosives.
Industrial grade fireworks.
It could blow up any minute.
- Cassie!
- It could blow up any minute.
Cassie!
This place has
always been a death trap.
- I got you, man.
- Come on. This way. Get her out.
Otherwise stable.
Wait, wait, wait.
Check his abdomen.
And internal injuries.
Good catch.
Let's go. Come on.
I gotta get my guys in there.
The structure's unstable.
Hey, the people are trapped.
The place is
packed with explosives.
Industrial grade fireworks.
This place has
always been a death trap.
Cassie!
Cassie! Cassie.
I need you at the triage.
- Come down to the staging area.
- We're ready to go.
Sir, you're okay. You're okay.
He's stable. Ready to transport.
Yeah, copy that. We need
every able body down here.
You're gonna be okay.
Stabilise the head while
I get the longboard set up.
- Yeah. I'll give you a hand.
- Wait. O'Neil!
Copy that.
Hey, what is it? I gotta roll.
Will you let me drive?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I just have a weird feeling.
Cassie, I need you over here.
Will you just let me drive?
Look, you had
a bad experience on the job.
I don't think
that's what's happening.
Don't let it
mess with your head.
Cassie, come on!
This is O'Neil.
Clear of dock side.
Headed back...
O'Neil, come on.
Come on. O'Neil.
Come on!
Let's get it! Come on, let's go!
Wake up!
O'Neil, come on.
Did you see a white light or...
Cassie! Cassie!
Come on. Come back.
Come on, come on.
- Ben, help me.
- Cassie, Cassie, it's okay.
It's all right. It's okay.
It's okay. Okay?
There's nothing
you could have done. Okay?
So, was it worth the trouble?
The scale
of the NSA surveillance
is unprecedented.
They can access everything.
There's nowhere to hide.
That's the idea.
The potential is infinite.
It's intoxicating.
But, in the wrong hands,
I mean...
people can be tracked
wherever they go.
It's gonna change everything.
As long as it has the ability
to find those women now...
before they get their powers.
This is what
they look like in your visions
as well as you can recollect.
Their faces have been
taunting me for years.
We don't know exactly
when your vision takes place...
so I'm giving us
a 10-year range just to be safe.
Here's what
they should look like now.
They're younger than I thought.
I didn't know
we'd be targeting teenagers.
They're teenagers now,
but in the future...
they have powers,
and they will try to destroy me.
I came from nothing,
less than nothing.
I will not give up
everything I've built...
and have my life cut short.
Well, if they ride
public transportation...
go to a museum...
get money from an ATM...
wherever they are
in the world...
Find them.
I pay you a fortune.
Yeah, I'll find them.
Still no blurriness.
No double vision.
No discolouration at all.
Your eyesight is good,
and all your other vitals
check out.
But what about the visions?
How am I seeing that stuff?
Sometimes when
we experience trauma,
it can have a lasting effect.
This isn't trauma.
I knew he was gonna die.
I saw it.
Cassie, I have
all your reports here
from your other consultations.
Your head CT was normal.
Your MRI was clear.
The scan showed
no abnormalities.
I know that it sounds crazy,
I know,
but I don't understand
what's happening.
I will be recommending
that you take a week off.
Get some rest.
Watch old movies.
If you still have concerns,
I can run some bloods
or refer you to psych.
But I'm sure
everything will be back
to normal before you know it.
I am in the presence
of the Spirit of Christmas
Yet-to-Come.
And you're going to show me
shadows of things
that have not yet happened
but will happen.
Spirit of the Future,
I fear you more than
any other spectre I've seen.
But even in my fear,
I must tell you, I am too old.
I cannot change.
Whose funeral
were they talking about?
Hey, Cass, it's me again. Ben.
I know you're there.
Just pick up.
I ought to be there
this time of day.
Okay, well, O'Neil's funeral
starts at 2:00 in Poughkeepsie.
Everyone's going.
I know it's the last place
you wanna be...
but it would help Susan
if you came.
It might help you too.
Look, if you leave now,
you can still make it.
Cassie?
Cass?
Before I draw
nearer to that stone,
answer me one question.
Are these the shadows
of things that must be...
or are they only shadows
of things that might be?
Hate to break it to you,
Scrooge...
but you can't change anything.
Are these the shadows of things
that must be?
Or are they only shadows
of things that might be?
This isn't gonna
change anything.
Guess you didn't die after all.
Please keep all
personal belongings with you
throughout your trip.
Come on, guys. This way.
Come on. Let's go down the ramp.
Yeah, awesome.
Can I have one
to Poughkeepsie, please?
...New Haven now ready.
Track 25. All aboard.
Please keep all
personal belongings with you
throughout your trip.
Anya Corazón is now moving
onto the platform.
She's on her own.
Julia Cornwall is
on the concourse, also alone.
...find a member
of the MTA staff.
And Martha Franklin.
Shit.
What are the odds of them
all being in the same place
at the same time?
It's not a coincidence.
There must be something
that connects them.
Or...
something that will.
Please keep all belongings
with you at all times.
If you see something suspicious,
find a member of the MTA staff.
- Just on the lower level?
- Oh, sorry.
Train to New Haven now ready.
Track 25.
All aboard.
New York City is a whole
new level of crazy these days.
Please keep all belongings
with you at all times.
If you see something suspicious,
find a member of the...
So this is two case studies?
Train to New Haven now ready.
Track 25.
All aboard.
All right. Well, sit there,
and I'll take this seat.
Train to New Haven now ready.
Track 25.
All aboard.
This is the train
to Mount Vernon, right?
Oh, my God.
Train to New Haven now ready.
Track 25.
- Is this real?
- All aboard.
Are you okay, dear?
Oh, God,
I think I'm going crazy.
New York City is a whole
new level of crazy these days.
This is the train
to Mount Vernon, right?
I hope not.
Mount Vernon train
will be leaving
in three minutes, Track 8.
Hey, get back.
Yeah, they're coming your way.
...all belongings
with you at all times.
If you see something suspicious,
find a member of the MTA staff.
Get up! Get off! Get off!
- Get up!
- Me?
Go! Get off! You're gonna die
if you stay here!
- Get up!
- We are? Are you threatening us?
This is an emergency situation.
I need you
to follow my instructions.
Get off the train.
Come on.
My mom told me
never to talk to strangers.
- Get up!
- Hey, give me that back!
Hey, give me that back!
I am so pressing charges.
Okay, knock yourself out.
Give me
my freaking skateboard back.
Let's go.
What? No.
Okay, never mind.
Give me
my freaking skateboard back.
Okay...
- What exactly is this emergency?
- Well...
This woman's
trying to abduct us!
What?
No, that's not... That's...
Shh. That's...
That's your emergency. That.
Is anybody else seeing this?
- That man is trying to kill you.
- And how do you...
- Why?
- I don't know. Come on.
We don't have
tickets for this train.
That's your biggest concern?
Please stand clear
of the closing doors.
This train is departing.
Please be kind. Remove your bags
from the empty seats.
Place them
in the luggage rack above.
Come on.
Okay.
Hey, am I on the right train?
I don't know, man.
Please have all tickets ready.
This is Metro North to North...
Hey, what are you doing?
No! Help!
Holy shit.
Come on.
Go.
Run!
There's an emergency exit
to the street that way.
Go.
Hey, help. Over here.
I've never been so happy
to see cops.
You guys
need to call for backup.
That will not be necessary
as long as you cooperate.
Wait. What?
No, it's not for me. Ow.
No. You don't understand.
- Don't worry, don't worry. Calm down.
- We're being attacked. We're being attacked.
You're safe.
Run! Go!
Run!
Run! Run!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on.
- Get in.
- What?
- Here you go. Thank you so much.
- Get in.
Thank you so much.
This is for you.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Move. Slide over.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Oh, wow, thank...
Hey!
That guy was nuts. Do you guys
think he killed those cops?
He could climb on walls
and dodge bullets.
- How is that even possible?
- It's not.
There's not enough
frictional force
in the bare human foot
to overcome gravity...
and keep him
stuck to the wall...
- What the hell is going on?
- ...much less the ceiling.
Yeah, well,
science didn't seem to stop him,
so what good is it?
- What good is science?
- Okay, enough.
- Please, don't fight.
- Enough.
- No, I was just telling them...
- Enough!
Your voices are, like,
drilling in the centre
of my skull...
and I need to think.
I'm Cassie. Okay?
What are your names?
I'm Julia Cornwall.
My dad lives here in New York,
and my mom lives
back in LA, but...
We don't need
your whole life story.
I'm Anya Corazón.
Mattie Franklin.
- Thank you for protecting us.
- No, no, no.
I'm not... That's not...
That's not
what's happening here.
I'm not protecting you.
I am, I am...
Your parents can handle this.
My parents
are on a business trip.
Yeah.
My parents are out of town too.
- My dad is busy working, so...
- Oh, my God.
I was gonna go
stay with some friends.
Well, where do
your friends live?
- I'll drop you off first.
- ...are asking
for the public's help...
in finding a person of interest
seen in the attack
on multiple NYPD officers...
at Grand Central Terminal
this afternoon.
That's great. Good.
I hope they find his crazy ass.
That was insane.
They better lock him up.
Right? I mean...
She is also the same person
police are
seeking to question...
in the possible abduction...
- She?
- ...of the three teenage girls.
Eyewitnesses have identified
the woman in her early 30s.
The public has been asked
for any information...
What?
...and to keep an eye out
for these girls.
What? That's...
But you guys... What about them?
And he was
crawling on the ceiling.
What about that guy?
I mean, you saw. I...
No one saw ceiling guy.
Everyone thinks
you're the kidnapper.
Yeah, because
you told them I was.
I didn't know
what was happening.
Okay, guys.
My uncle, Jonah, can totally
help us. I'm gonna call him.
You have a phone?
You know they can
track those nowadays, right?
No, you can't...
- Hey! You can't do that.
- She's right.
It's okay.
Daddy will buy you a new one.
What is your problem?
- What do you mean?
- Please.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Okay.
Anyone who wants to leave
can leave right now.
- Yo, watch out!
- Okay.
- Wait.
- Lady, drive!
Sorry.
No, you can't actually leave...
because you guys
are the only ones
that know
what actually happened.
Okay, well, this is
what we're gonna do, okay?
We're just gonna, like,
lay low for a little bit.
And...
I'll figure out
how to get out of this.
You know...
This is still not a kidnapping.
Okay?
Feels like a kidnapping.
How did they get away?
It's like
they knew I was coming.
No hits at the train station,
bus depot,
or any of the bridges.
Wherever they went,
there aren't any cameras.
The police don't have
this technology.
You have access
to every camera in the city.
We should be ahead of them.
I went to a lot of trouble
to steal you these tools.
Use them better.
I've always
wanted to be a Girl Scout.
Of course you did.
Anybody else starving?
All I have is gum.
Here. I found this
in the glove compartment.
Wait. That bag's
already been opened.
We don't know
how long it's been in there.
Okay, I hope you're
good at catching squirrels.
Okay, so what's the deal
with ceiling guy?
I told you, I don't know.
I've never seen him before.
Then how did you know
he was coming?
Oh, my God.
I'm kind of more interested
in why he's trying to kill us.
I don't know.
Crazy shit's been happening,
and I don't know why.
Stop asking me. Okay?
Wait. You're the paramedic.
You saved my stepmother,
then you were
super awkward about it.
That does sound like me.
Wait. I recognise you too.
What?
Yeah. You live in my building.
You leave your junk mail
in the lobby...
and then everybody else
has to clean it up for you.
Okay. Well, there should be
a recycling bin there.
You don't think this is weird?
That we both know you?
It's honestly, like,
the least weird thing
that's happened all day.
What?
Total stranger.
No.
You flipped me off.
That's not really
narrowing it down much.
You guys, this is so freaky.
Who are you? What is going on?
I can see the future.
Kind of.
I mean...
What the hell?
See? She didn't see that coming.
It doesn't work like that.
You guys,
just give her a chance, please.
Wait. When you were looking
into the future...
did you see us...
in the middle of nowhere
eating glove-compartment jerky?
Okay, look. Believe me or don't.
I don't care.
I didn't ask
to be doing this with you.
And I didn't ask for this
to happen to me, either.
Also, I'm pretty sure
I saved all of your lives.
So, you're welcome.
How does it work?
It just happens.
Can you do it now?
I can't control it.
You know the other guy can walk
on the ceiling, right?
No, he can't.
He was using his hands.
Why are you like this?
I'm just saying
it was more of a crawl.
It was like a spider...
person.
I'm gonna be back
in a few hours.
Where are you going?
I need to check some things out
about all of this.
You can't just leave us here.
We'll be okay, Julia.
We don't need a babysitter.
Yeah, sure. Just three teenagers
alone in the woods.
Definitely not the opening
of a horror film.
You are way safer out here.
Just, you know,
be like a Girl Scout girl.
Be that. Just be that.
Can you bring us
some sandwiches?
Cassie.
Can we trust you?
Three hours. Okay?
Just stay here.
And don't do anything dumb.
Seriously. Don't do dumb things.
She was talking to you.
Okay, well,
you're just a bitch, so...
I know tae kwon do.
You?
Yeah, I had
a few rough years in school
when my parents were divorcing.
So I wanted to feel like I could
fight back if I needed to.
That's what I thought.
One second, cat.
Come on.
Research on Amazonian spiders...
peptides, more peptides.
Come on. Where is it?
Spider people.
'Las Arañas'.
Have you ever heard
of 'Las Arañas'?
Me neither.
"According to local folklore...
"they possess powers
derived from spider venom...
"and are incredibly fast,
incredibly strong...
"and they can
climb like spiders."
Just like ceiling guy.
How would you know...
if you could climb a wall
if you've never tried?
Okay, let's not
mention that to anybody.
'"Las Arañas' are said to possess
a sixth sense...
"as if they had the ability
to glimpse the future."
Oh, my God.
Hey, who's got the jerky?
You ate it all.
I had, like, three pieces.
- Out of five.
- You counted?
You also ate all mine.
- What's this?
- Stop.
Stop. Just...
Jeez.
Okay, forget jerky.
Did you guys see that diner
like a half-mile down the road?
Let's just go there
and get real food.
- Cassie told us to stay here.
- Come on, Julia.
She bailed on us.
We don't have any money, genius.
Well, I have money, so...
You have money
so we should do what you want?
You got something to say?
You know,
I bet your dad is a senator
and your mom
sits on the board at the Met.
And you summer in the Hamptons
next to Martha Stewart.
So sad about Martha Stewart.
My parents are in Beijing...
where my dad
is raking in a ton of money
for making plastics
that pollute the ocean...
and my mom is spending it all
on hideous art.
So...
I talk to them on Mondays.
So who do you live with?
The housekeeper.
Well, on the upside, no curfew.
I bet you have
your own room at least.
I live with my dad and his wife
and their kid.
- What about your mom?
- She's...
not really around.
She bailed on you?
Right. So, diner?
We spend some of Mattie's
daddy's pollution money?
Yay.
I'm going to order
everything on the menu.
Julia, you in?
Hey.
We have
to take care of ourselves.
Yeah.
You're right.
Let's go do this.
She's kind of cute
when she's mad.
I heard that.
You are making
the right decision, Julia.
You will not like me
when I'm hangry.
Who says we like you now?
God! I knew
we shouldn't have done this.
Shit.
Do you think there's ticks?
Can we walk
- a little faster, please?
- Julia.
You said this was a shortcut.
Are we lost?
Do you know where you're going?
- You know where you're going?
- Yeah. Actually, I do.
Ow! Shit!
Okay. Don't talk
to anybody except to order.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
No one's gonna
track us down here.
Just don't make eye contact.
I hope they have cherry pie.
Let's sit at the bar.
There you go.
Here.
Should we make a game plan?
Eat first, strategise later.
Okay. Here you go.
Keep it coming.
Let's just eat quickly
and then get out of here.
Absolutely, great idea.
Right after cherry pie.
No. No cherry pie.
Julia, tell me you agree
that we should get dessert.
Yeah, whatever you guys
are arguing about...
I'm sure you're both
making really good points.
We have minestrone, we have clam
chowder, and we have tomato.
- Watch out, watch out.
- Ooh, she's lookin' at you.
We should go over there
and talk to them.
Really?
No. We...
Should we? We can't.
Come on. You know you want to.
No.
- This is not a good idea.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
- What're you doing?
- Yeah, what are you doing?
Just hold on a second.
What is this?
Do you want the Reuben?
It's just
a little confidence boost.
This isn't really my style.
So what? You look cute. Come on.
This is not a good idea.
Seriously, guys.
Okay.
Hi. Hey, guys.
- I'm Mattie. This is Julia.
- Oh, hey. Good.
- Can we sit?
- Yeah, of course.
We've been
saving these seats for you.
Awesome.
Oh, hey, what's up?
How you doin'?
Nice to meet you too.
...for your information.
Can you just
confirm your location?
4 Star Diner.
Daves Road, Route 206.
- Hey.
- Church Hill, New Jersey.
Possible sighting
in Church Hill, New Jersey.
Connect me with
the Church Hill police dispatch.
Yeah. Patching you in now.
2-2-3 dispatch.
On scene at 4 Star Diner.
Route 206 at Daves Road.
Go ahead, 2-2-3.
No need to send backup.
These aren't
our missing persons.
Code four. Repeat.
These are not
our missing persons.
Girls!
Oh, God damn it.
Let's go. Let's go!
Don't even pretend
that you're cooler than Britney.
I know you know the words.
- Come on, get up here.
- You should get up there.
So much
for not attracting attention.
No. Please. Please, stop.
Don't touch me, okay?
Can you...
What are you doing?
- What are you...
- What is that?
We have to go.
I'm so sorry.
Get down!
- This isn't what you think.
- Get your stuff.
You left us.
I'm so sorry.
Julia!
Julia, get back!
Come on!
No! Mattie!
No.
This track is going to be huge.
Are you in the zone?
This is Britney Spears.
Let's try that again.
I love this song.
Guys.
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I have to dance.
- Come on, Julia.
- Mattie, no.
Right. Okay.
Oh, my God. Come on.
Seriously, dude.
Come on. Let's go.
Don't even pretend
that you're cooler than Britney.
I know you know the words.
Come on, get up here.
Hey!
You should totally
get up there, dog.
Come on.
Hey!
Guys. Guys, guys.
We have to go, we have to...
Girls, get in! Get in! Get in!
Leave everything. Run!
- Come on, let's go. Let's go!
- Mattie, come on!
- Get in!
- I'm so sorry, Cassie.
God!
So much
for not needing a babysitter.
Do you guys think of anybody
but yourselves?
You're so impulsive
and entitled,
and you don't listen!
- We didn't mean to...
- Whatever!
Don't even say anything!
God!
Your futures were almost...
so different.
You're lucky I saw them.
I'm so sorry.
Yes.
You should be so sorry.
All of you should be sorry.
God!
Amaria, where did they go?
I'm running checks now.
I don't understand
how they're doing this.
I've got a match on the woman
who's with them.
I'm not interested in her.
Focus on finding those girls.
Cassandra Webb.
Daughter of Constance Webb, deceased.
Did you say, "Webb"?
Yeah. Do you know her?
That's not possible.
Come on.
He's not gonna stop
until he kills us, is he?
I don't know what he wants.
I don't know anything.
But you can see the future.
Can't you stop him
with your visions?
I don't know
how to control them.
It's useless.
Well, we're alive.
Maybe that's a plus.
Is your hand okay?
It's fine.
First thing in the morning,
I'm taking you all home.
Your parents can deal with this.
No, they can't.
My mom's in a psych ward.
She didn't really cope well
after my dad left...
and so, I got sent to live
with him and his new family...
and I don't think
that they want me there.
I wondered if they missed me...
if I ran away.
So you did.
My parents aren't around either.
I think they resent how having
a kid messed up their lives.
I don't think they're gonna
fly back from China
to deal with this.
And I really
don't wanna find out, so...
I'm on my own.
Well, fine.
Then you guys can just...
- go to the police.
- No.
My dad got deported
six months ago.
I came home from school,
and he was gone.
What about your mom?
My mom died when I was five.
It's just me and my dad.
Except he never told me
he didn't have his papers.
So, I've just been
living by myself
at our apartment since then.
You're on your own?
I don't need anyone else
to look out for me.
And I don't
have a curfew, either.
So, I can't go to the police.
Okay?
Until I'm 18, I can't exist.
And there's no way
I'm getting deported too.
Or going into the foster system.
Well...
Foster system
isn't always that terrible.
Things didn't turn out
so bad for me.
Right.
Cassie, please help us.
No one survives once enough
poison enters their system.
You won't be so lucky next time.
Why are you doing this?
I need to stop them
from killing me.
They're not killers.
They're just teenagers.
In the future,
they become much more.
In the future, they will destroy
me and everything I've built.
Those girls cannot exist.
How come you get to decide?
Because I'm the one
with the powers.
If you knew what I knew,
you'd do the same thing.
Would I?
If I knew the price to pay
was the lives of three girls?
The only thing I know is that,
in the future,
they also have powers.
The girls? The girls have powers
in the future?
Did you think you could beat me
with your mind?
Your mother underestimated me.
The power of the spider.
Don't make the same mistake.
Tell me where they are!
They don't mean anything to you.
You could just walk away.
What is this?
Rise and shine.
Okay, so this guy's hands
somehow release
an acute neurotoxin...
and it is painful. I was lucky.
The longer he holds on to you,
the more poison
gets into your system.
Then what happens?
Then your heart stops.
But you can offset
cardiac arrest with CPR.
So you interlock your hands
like this.
You lock your elbows...
and then you place
the heel of your hand
right on the sternum. Okay?
And then you pump.
And you wanna go,
like, two inches down.
And you wanna keep
a rhythm like a heartbeat. Okay?
You ready?
Okay, begin compressions.
Go. Good.
Okay. And when do I stop?
You don't stop.
If you stop, they die.
And if you get tired,
then you need
somebody to take over.
- I'm getting kinda tired.
- Okay.
- Anya, get ready to take over.
- Mmm-hmm.
But you have to pick up
the exact same rhythm.
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- Yep.
- And go.
Great. Nice, Mattie.
Not cool.
Julia, you wanna take over?
Okay.
Get ready.
Okay. One, two, three. Perfect.
Nice job, Anya.
I've never said this before
in my entire life...
but you're a good teacher.
Well, I've been
learning some things too.
About my mom.
Wait, so you do know this guy.
My mom did. I think.
That's her.
She's really pretty.
So this is because of you?
All I know is that
she was researching spiders.
In her notebook,
there's some stuff...
about a local tribe in Peru
that can do, like, crazy stuff.
What kind of crazy stuff?
Climb like spiders.
So is he one of them?
I need more information.
You're leaving.
I have to go and figure out
what is going on.
How?
You have to go to Peru.
I'll be gone a week.
I don't wanna leave them,
but he's out there
looking for them...
and they're relying on me,
and I don't know how else
to protect them.
Okay, look, I'm staying
with Mary for a few weeks
while Richard's out of town.
He won't find them there.
But, Cassie...
I can't pretend to understand
what's going on here.
Just be careful, okay?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Thank you, Ben.
You didn't ask for any of this.
Okay, well, neither did you.
You have come back
looking for answers.
Back?
I promised your mother
I would be here.
My mom thought
'Las Arañas' were a myth.
What do you think?
I think she was crazy
for coming here alone.
She came here
hoping to extract healing
properties from the spiders.
She thought
she was being protected.
By Ezekiel Sims?
His motives were selfish.
He used your mom to find us.
But, because
he stole the spider...
he was cursed.
And he's been trying to outrun
his destiny ever since.
This is where my mom died?
And where you were born.
I don't understand why
she risked my life to come here.
To see the future clearly...
you have
to heal the wounds of your past.
That sounds like literally
every therapy session
I've ever avoided.
You have to go
back to your beginning
and keep going past that.
There are powers
you don't even know
you're capable of.
Your thread did not start
when you were born.
Do you trust me?
Not really sure at this point
I have a choice.
You could just walk away.
Your thread did not start
when you were born.
They're almost
impossible to find.
She really is trying her best
to keep me from working.
Not when I'm this close.
But I'm not
gonna let her do that.
Why did you hate me so much?
Thank you.
For the umbrella.
- Give it to me.
- No.
I found it.
I found the spider.
Incredible, isn't it?
- Give it to me.
- No, please.
Give it to me.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- You could just walk away.
- No, you're making the wrong...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
'Las Arañas' could not stand by.
We tried to save you both.
Her journey will not be easy...
but she is strong.
Your test results came back.
I'm sorry to tell you
that your baby has
myasthenia gravis.
It's a genetic
neuromuscular disorder.
But I don't have
a neuromuscular disorder.
Life expectancy varies.
Do you need a tissue?
No. No. I need a cure.
I'm afraid there is no cure.
Single target
nucleotide intervention.
It's experimental...
but there are some promising
leads in the Amazon.
That's why you went there?
For me?
I have to advise you against
travelling in your condition.
I'm sorry, what are you offering
besides tissues?
I know this is hard to accept.
No, no, I am...
I'm unwilling to accept
a diagnosis of helplessness.
And I'm not gonna
teach my daughter to either.
You did it.
I never knew I was sick.
The spider venom
did have healing properties.
I'm so sorry I spent so long
being mad at you.
I always thought my mom
didn't care about me.
Sometimes you must sacrifice
yourself for those you love.
I was there.
I was in the room...
I was in the room with her.
How did you do that?
'You' did that.
Now you're starting to see
what you're capable of.
You came here to learn the truth
about your past.
But you will leave ready
to embrace your future.
Seeing into the future
is no match for Ezekiel.
I need to stop him
before he kills those girls.
But I can't do what he can do.
I can't do the leapy, crawly,
like, death poison.
You didn't get the gift of
the greater physical strength...
or the ability
to release poison...
but seeing into the future
is only the start.
Your mind
has infinite potential.
If you master your power,
you can use the web...
to be in more than one place
at the same time.
You are the only one
who can change the future.
And when you take on
the responsibility...
great power will come.
Every day that goes by,
my appointment with death
gets closer.
And you still
have found nothing?
How can she have kept
three teenagers
hidden for a week?
I'm running checks
every three minutes,
scanning CCTV camera.
I have hacked
police and emergency services
frequencies.
I have eyes
on all of their houses,
including friends and family.
Still nothing.
Do you understand?
Huh?
Those girls cannot exist.
They will try to destroy me,
as I will you
if you don't find them.
She can't hide them forever.
Okay, it's still
pretty quiet out there.
- What'd I miss?
- Ben said words.
- Oh, boring.
- Okay, let's try and remember
- to pick up...
- Nice nails.
- after ourselves. Okay, guys?
- Thank you.
- Hey!
- I mean, this is really...
- Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Rude!
- All right, throwing popcorn...
- Guys?
- is super fun.
- I cannot wait for that.
- But I also think...
- Guys, either I peed myself...
or my water broke.
Ew!
Well, honestly,
you probably peed yourself...
because that isn't
supposed to happen yet.
Richard's not here,
and the baby
isn't due for four weeks.
I don't think the baby
got the memo, Ben.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
Looks like we may have to wait
a little while for...
the ambulance.
The baby is not waiting.
He's coming now.
Now.
Like, here? In the dining room?
If Ben doesn't get me
to the hospital, then yes.
Okay.
Get in the car.
Keep your head down.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay. Come on.
Okay, okay.
Everyone okay?
Okay, seat belts, everybody.
Seriously?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Never mind.
All right, let's step on it.
10-58 in progress. 30-relo-5.
I might have something.
Woman in labour.
20-Edward copy. En route.
- 13-Edward, go ahead.
- 10-4.
Possible D&D in progress.
I've intercepted
a call to the hospital.
St Timothy's.
Track the route.
Tracking.
The baby is not waiting.
...doesn't get me
to the hospital, then...
Get out, get out, get out!
- Go, go, go!
- Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
What? What?
Mattie, Mattie, Mattie!
Shit!
Sorry, guys.
Hey!
Thank you.
So the last one was
three minutes and 24 seconds
after the previous one.
So that means
the time between contractions
is reducing at a rate of...
21.6 seconds.
That's pretty fast.
You better hurry up 'cause
I'm not sticking around...
- if it gets gross.
- Okay.
He's heading southwest
on Vernon Avenue.
I'll cut them off at
the Second Avenue intersection.
Drive faster.
Let's go. Let's go, please.
Hack into traffic control.
Turn the lights green.
Amaria, now.
Turning all traffic lights
to green.
Why is no one stopping? Hey!
Ben, watch out!
- They're not stopping.
- What's happening?
Whoa, whoa.
Ben!
Everyone okay?
Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
What is that?
Oh, my God, it's him.
Guys.
- Ben, go, go, go!
- Everybody get out right now!
- Get out, get out, get out!
- Go, go!
Cassie!
Get out. Go on.
Get in the ambulance. Go.
- Come on.
- It's not over. Go.
Ben, I need you to get Mary
as far away from us as possible.
Okay? Ezekiel,
he won't care about you now.
Well, what about you?
I liked it better
when you didn't make plans.
You're showing off.
Not yet.
I think we lost him.
Get in the back
and charge the AED.
- For what?
- Just do it. Go.
Okay, press "charge."
Am I having a heart attack?
I think
I'm having a heart attack.
You're not gonna
have a heart attack.
Hey, man!
Okay, get ready.
Get it close to the ceiling.
Nobody touch the sides
or anything.
- Ready?
- Okay. Yep, yep.
Wait. Wait.
Now.
Sorry.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Now you're showing off.
Maybe a little.
Now what?
Those girls cannot exist.
- ...doesn't look safe.
- It's a death trap.
...infinite potential.
This place has
always been a death trap.
...packed with explosives.
Get down!
Go! Run!
Jump! Come on!
Get in the helicopter.
I have a code 30. PD-36-307.
Requesting airlift support.
Dockside, Queens.
Copy that.
Okay.
It's gonna get a little crazy.
It's already crazy.
You didn't bail on us.
Whatever happens,
I promise
I'm going to protect you guys.
We'll protect each other.
Yeah, we're in this together.
Right?
Yeah.
Okay. We are still
not doing a high five.
I know. It's not cool.
Let's go. Out the back.
- What?
- Go, go, go.
This doesn't look safe.
Well, it's full of explosives
and it's structurally unsound.
That doesn't 'sound' safe.
It's a death trap.
And that's a good thing?
As long as we're not the ones
who get trapped.
No matter what happens...
we need to work together, okay?
We're listening this time,
Cassie.
Yeah, and we won't be impulsive.
Are we ready?
We have to get to the roof.
He's gonna be here any minute.
Here. Take these.
Put them in
as many crates as you can.
Okay?
You two, go that way.
We need to slow him down.
- Mattie, this way.
- You come with me. Come on.
I got this one.
Come on, Julia. Let's go.
Anya, go.
Go.
Go straight ahead.
When I say "now," get down.
What do you mean?
It's a dead end.
Now!
Whoa!
Go! Run!
Now you're really showing off.
Come on, upstairs.
I knew. I knew she had a plan.
- Hey!
- We're here!
Down here!
Make your way to the south side.
Come on.
Wait. Get down!
Let's go. He said south side.
We can go this way.
Anya, stop!
- Let's go!
- Mattie!
- We need to go this way.
- Go down here.
Get down!
Go to the ladder. Go!
Come on, come on!
Use the web.
Get to the helicopter.
- Hey!
- Wait! Girls! Get down!
It's not safe to land.
You'll have to get higher.
Guys, this way.
We can get to the chopper
from up there.
Anya, jump.
Jump now! Julia, get back!
Julia, get down!
Oh, God!
You should have walked away.
You can't protect them.
Cassie!
Over here, asshole.
Mattie!
Don't hurt her!
Anya!
Cassie!
You can't save all three.
And when you take on
the responsibility...
great power will come.
Julia, I got you.
Come on.
Mattie. You're gonna be okay.
Anya. Anya, give me your hand.
You still can't beat me
with your mind.
What makes you so sure?
Come on. Come on, come on.
You're just like your mother.
Yes, I am.
You've been trying
to change your future.
But the girls
were never your future.
I was.
No!
No. Cassie!
She's not breathing.
- Her heart's not beating.
- We know what to do.
Beginning compressions.
Interlock your fingers.
Come back, Cassie.
Come on, guys. Come on!
Keep going. We don't stop.
Come on, Cassie.
I'm getting a little tired.
Okay. I'm right here.
Cassie, wake up! Please.
- Cassie!
- Come back, Cassie.
We're here, Cassie.
We're not leaving you.
Cassie, you got this.
Please. I need you. Please.
Oh, my God!
Cassie.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, my God. We did it.
We did it.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, he's perfect.
He is.
- He's perfect.
- Yeah.
We're still here, Cassie.
Yeah. We're not leaving you.
I wouldn't be here
if it weren't
for the three of you.
Right back at ya.
Ben said to tell you
that the baby
is doing really well.
And he's loving being an uncle.
Yeah. All the fun
and none of the responsibility.
That's what he thinks.
Are you all immediate family?
Yes.
They're all mine.
Can we get you anything?
No.
I have everything I need
right here.
No.
You left your junk mail
downstairs again.
And we got takeout.
But we didn't know...
Kung Pao chicken is perfect.
How'd you know?
Bless you, Anya.
What?
Thank you.
Mattie!
What? I told you I'm starving.
And I told you guys
that you wouldn't...
...wouldn't like you
if you were hangry.
Well, you wouldn't, so...
How's your eyesight?
I can see better
than I ever have.
Oh, yeah?
Can you see us in the future?
Yes.
I can see you.
Standing up
for what you believe.
Never giving up.
Discovering you were always
more powerful than you thought.
Nothing I didn't already know.
I don't know about you two...
but that totally
makes sense to me.
- What? I'm serious.
- Wow.
What? I'm being serious.
Oh, wow. Okay. Wow.
Whatever the future holds...
we'll be ready.
And you know the best thing
about the future?
It hasn't happened yet.
Downloaded from YTS.MX
Modify by Blue-Bird™